{
    "subject": "resource/A_Price_Above_Rubies",
    "predicate": "property/writer",
    "object": "resource/Boaz_Yakin",
    "human_readable": "The writer of 'A Price Above Rubies' is Boaz Yakin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7746390700340271,
            "question": "What is the name of the screenwriter who wrote 'A Price Above Rubies'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7738168239593506,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for 'A Price Above Rubies'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5972720980644226,
            "question": "Is Boaz Yakin known for writing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274697542190552,
            "question": "Can you name another film written by Boaz Yakin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5158239006996155,
            "question": "What genre is 'A Price Above Rubies' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48185810446739197,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the title 'A Price Above Rubies' and the film's plot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4297880232334137,
            "question": "How has 'A Price Above Rubies' been received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4285813271999359,
            "question": "What year was 'A Price Above Rubies' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38268718123435974,
            "question": "Has Boaz Yakin won any awards for his writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3227611780166626,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Boaz Yakin's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of 'A Price Above Rubies' is Boaz Yakin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7934_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Boaz Yakin won any awards for his writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7934_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'A Price Above Rubies' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7934_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has 'A Price Above Rubies' been received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7934_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7934_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Boaz Yakin is the writer and director of \"A Price Above Rubies.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}